be careful of people whose generosity only extends from their dominance.
You know, like you'll have people that you think are your friends and they'll be generous, right?
They'll be like, oh, like we family, like, you know, we share, et cetera, et cetera. But they
only do that from a place of, I am in the capability of giving to you. You are receiving
from me. And it's, it's something that is very nuanced. But when you realize it, you're like,
hold up. Oh, this person, like, this is like a top down type. Because when the role is flipped
and you are wanting something from them where you are in the place of dominance,
watch how they don't show up. Watch how they move in a way to have some sort of like power struggle.
Just watch. I mean, this is something I've recently just experienced. And when I brought it to the
person's attention, they vehemently denied it, but they definitely didn't want to hear about it.
And they definitely didn't try to figure out.